EZ MICHAEL YUCOR



- WEB DEVELOPER
- GRAPHIC DESIGNER

CONTACT INFO

- ezmichaely@gmail.com
- +63 926 831 909
- Purok 4, San Miguel, Bacong
- github.com/ezmichaely
- in linkedin.com/in/ezmichaely
- portfolio-ezmichaely.vercel.app

SKILLS































•

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

 The Sisters of Mary School BOYSTOWN

Major in Computer Hardware Servicing NCII 2007 - 2011

Negros Oriental State
University

BS in Information Technology 2017 - 2023

ABOUT ME

With a solid foundation in computer programming and a deep enthusiasm for crafting web applications, coupled with experience in full stack development, honed skills, and meticulous focus, I'm enthusiastically looking forward to becoming part of a collaborative work setting that fosters my professional growth and facilitates the enhancement of my chosen career path.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

FREELANCER

May 2017 - Present

Key responsibilities:

- Developed a system for students capstone and other projects for Korean Manager.
- Created a tarpaulin for my clients and redesigned their brochure and leaflets.
- Designed a various logo for their new business companies.
- Repair and Install System Software.

NEGROS ORIENTAL RESEARCH DEVELOPMENT CENTER DEPT OF AGRICULTURE (NORDC-DA)

September 2021 - December 2021

Key responsibilities:

- Designed a various layouts for tarpaulin and brochure promotions and leaflets.
- Analyzed the farmer's data to make an appropriate ID card designs for them.

CONSTRUER ENGINEERING SERVICES / TAYOKTOK RESTO – CAFÉ

October 2022 - December 2022

Key responsibilities:

- Analyzed the surveyed lot data and plot it in the AutoCAD.
- Assisted the surveyors and managed the financial expenses.
- Managed the FB Page and created a Brochure promotions.